Guide to the Duke Real Estate Office records, 1893-2018 and undated UA.10.04.0007
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Real Estate Deeds, 1893-2018; undated
  - File No.: 470, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: H. R. Byrd, Type: Deed, 1946 August 13 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 167, Page: 35, Comments/Location: Lancaster Avenue
  - File No.: 471, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Joe Matthews, Type: Deed, 1946 September 25 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 17-18
  - File No.: 472, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Joe Matthews, Type: Deed, 1947 April 24 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 5-6
  - File No.: 473, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: S. W. Myatt, Type: Deed, 1946 September 26 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 168, Page: 298, Comments/Location: Anderson Street
  - File No.: 474, Grantee: Robert Fearing, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 June 2 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-9
  - File No.: 475, Grantee: Walter Gordy, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 June 2 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-5
  - File No.: 476, Grantee: James H. Phillips, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 June 2 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-25
  - File No.: 477, Grantee: John H. Saylor, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 June 2 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-22
  - File No.: 478, Grantee: William V. Smith, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 June 2 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-21
  - File No.: 479, Grantee: Charles E. Ward, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 June 2 (Box 9)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-12
  - File No.: 480, Grantee: Juan R. Castellano, Grantor: Franklin Young, Type: Deed, 1949 April 11 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 481, Grantee: Leslie B. Hohman, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 June 19 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-7
  - File No.: 482, Grantee: Jasper Callaway, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 May 1 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Callaways
  - File No.: 483, Grantee: John Rudin, II, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 July 30 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-N
  - File No.: 484, Grantee: Harvey G. Taylor, Grantor: W. L. Foushee, Type: Deed, 1947 May 14 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Urban Avenue
  - File No.: 485, Grantee: Edward Simmons, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1916 September 7 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 23-24
  - File No.: 486, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Mary Hicks, Type: Deed, 1947 July 10 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 175, Page: 212, Comments/Location: Hermitage Court
  - File No.: 487, Grantee: Dorothy Kuder, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 October 4 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 26-27
  - File No.: 488, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: I. W. Bishop, Type: Warr/Deed, 1947 October 8 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 128, Page: 49, Comments/Location: Johnston's Corner
  - File No.: 489, Grantee: Donald S. Martin, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 December 3 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots H-2, 3&4
  - File No.: 490, Grantee: Charles H. Sawyer, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 November 5 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-6
  - File No.: 491, Grantee: Robert Nichols, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 November 16 (Box 10)
    County: Orange, Comments/Location: Highway 70
  - File No.: 492, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Vadie Nichols, Type: Warr/Deed, 1947 November 3 (Box 10)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 128, Page: 383, Comments/Location: Highway 10
  - File No.: 493, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Robert Nichols, Type: Warr/Deed, 1947 November 3 (Box 10)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 128, Page: 384, Comments/Location: Highway 10
  - File No.: 494, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: L. A. Tomlinson, Type: Deed, 1947 November 28 (Box 10)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 128, Page: 465
  - File No.: 495, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Robert H. Moore, Type: Warr/Deed, 1948 February 27 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 496, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Eno Cotton Mills, Type: Warr/Deed, 1948 February 24 (Box 10)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 129, Page: 43, Comments/Location: Along Highway 70
  - File No.: 497, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: J. L. Wilkins, Type: Deed, 1948 March 3 (Box 10)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 129, Page: 147, Comments/Location: Mineral Spring Road, Little Creek
  - File No.: 499, Grantee: Henry H. Lewis, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1948 June 3 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-20
  - File No.: 500, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Earl G. Mueller, Type: Deed, 1949 January 25 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 501, Grantee: B. F. Hester, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1948 April 5 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 502, Grantee: State of N.C., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1947 November 17
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: 10.31 acres, Comments/Location: Lenox Baker
  - File No.: 503, Grantee: R. H. Hester, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1948 April 5 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 504, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dorothy Edwards, Type: Deed, 1949 December 2 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-18
  - File No.: 505, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Blanch Smith, Type: Deed, 1949 November 25 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-19
  - File No.: 506, Grantee: Barney L. Jones, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1948 August 11 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-10
  - File No.: 507, Grantee: Harvey G. Taylor, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1948 August 16 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 92-94
  - File No.: 508, Grantee: Kenneth A. Podger, Grantor: Donald S. Martin, Type: Deed, 1948 December 6 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-B
  - File No.: 509, Grantee: George P. Cole, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1948 November 23 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 510, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Henry Lewis, Type: Deed, 1949 January 25 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 511, Grantee: Richard Watson, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1949 February 21 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 512, Grantee: Leon H. Ellis, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1949 March 16 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-15
  - File No.: 513, Grantee: Philip Handler, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1949 May 4 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-2, 3 & 4
  - File No.: 514, Grantee: Edward C. Horn, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1949 August 18 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-28
  - File No.: 515, Grantee: Ralph P. Morgan, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1949 August 18 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-29
  - File No.: 516, Grantee: Jackson Rambeau, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1949 September 8 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-14
  - File No.: 517, Grantee: Jessie H. Bufkin, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1949 September 8 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 518, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Kenneth Manning, Type: Deed, 1950 August 16 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 519, Grantee: Hubert T. Warren, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1949 December 9 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Pickett Road/0.88 acres
  - File No.: 520, Grantee: Robert N. Creadick, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 January 5 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-32 & 33
  - File No.: 521, Grantee: Dr. Bingham Dai, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1951 February 17 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-36
  - File No.: 524, Grantee: William A. Tyree, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 April 14 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 525, Grantee: Nicholas Georgiad, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 June 14 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-41
  - File No.: 526, Grantee: Jack B. Cahoon, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 July 5 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-38
  - File No.: 527, Grantee: James H. Phillips, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 July 17 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-6A
  - File No.: 528, Grantee: Walter Gordy, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 July 17 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-5A
  - File No.: 529, Grantee: Richard Predmore, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed/Copy, 1950 July 17 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-31
  - File No.: 530, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: James O. Cox, Jr., Type: Deed, 1951 January 26 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-39
  - File No.: 531, Grantee: Popular Apartments, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed/Copy, 1950 August 21 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: 29.96 acres, Comments/Location: Deed found/stored in #532 envelope
  - File No.: 532, Grantee: Popular Apartments, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 August 21 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: 29.96 acres, Comments/Location: Erwin Road
  - File No.: 534, Grantee: Victor J. Rudolph, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 October 13 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #3-A
  - File No.: 535, Grantee: James F. Cousins, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1950 September 19 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2
  - File No.: 536, Grantee: Eugene Greuling, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1951 February 17 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 537, Grantee: Benjamin Boyce, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1951 January 29 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 538, Grantee: James O. Cox, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed/Copy, 1951 January 26 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-17
  - File No.: 539, Grantee: Roger F. Anderson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed/Copy, 1951 February 2 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-1
  - File No.: 540, Grantee: H. Max Schiebel, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1951 April 5 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: 0.283 acres, Comments/Location: Cranford and Anderson Streets
  - File No.: 541, Grantee: Theodore W. Minah, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1951 May 1 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 542, Grantee: City of Durham, Grantor: Duke, 1951 April 28 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 198, Page: 199, Comments/Location: Withdrawal of Land/West Club
  - File No.: 543, Grantee: Lloyd B. Saville, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1951 February 11 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot 1 &.5 of 2, Comments/Location: Auburn Street
  - File No.: 544, Grantee: Everette J. Mann, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1951 May 16 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2, Comments/Location: Anderson Street
  - File No.: 545, Grantee: Elias Torre, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 June 10 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #4
  - File No.: 546, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: William D. Murray, Type: Deed, 1952 May 31 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 547, Grantee: Frances C. Brown, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1951 September 14 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 548, Grantee: Gladys D. Graves, Grantor: Duke, Type: LTR, 1964 April 29 (Box 10)
    County: Moore, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 5-6, Comments/Location: Fairway Drive, Southern Pines
  - File No.: 549, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Price Family, Type: Deed, 1951 October 11 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 202, Page: 303, Comments/Location: Old Morreene Dairy Road
  - File No.: 550, Grantee: Thomas Cordle, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed/Copy, 1951 October 19 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Perkins Road
  - File No.: 552, Grantee: United States of America, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1952 February 15 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: 0.961 acres/Erwin Road
  - File No.: 553, Grantee: William W. Shingleton, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1952 June 3 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 554, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Dr. H. C. Carr, Type: Warr/Deed, 1952 March 5 (Box 10)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 140, Page: 84, Comments/Location: New Hope Church Street
  - File No.: 556, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Charlie Cannada, Type: Deed, 1952 May 10 (Box 10)
    County: Orange, Deed Book: 141, Page: 106, Comments/Location: Duke Forest
  - File No.: 557, Grantee: William E. Whitford, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1952 November 10 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 558, Grantee: Hunter Jones, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1952 November 10 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #4-A
  - File No.: 559, Grantee: Lucius A Bigelow, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1952 December 15 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #36
  - File No.: 560, Grantee: Robert H. Connery, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 January 20 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 561, Grantee: Robert S. Rankin, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 January 20 (Box 10)
  - File No.: 562, Grantee: John Glasson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 April 1 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2-A
  - File No.: 563, Grantee: Earl T. Hanson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 April 1 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #1-A
  - File No.: 564, Grantee: T. C. Pegram, Grantor: Duke, 1966 February 22 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Rlse. Restric. Covenants/1129 Anderson
  - File No.: 565, Grantee: Jean Jack Demorest, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 May 26 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #47
  - File No.: 566, Grantee: Charles R. Vail, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 May 26 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #52
  - File No.: 567, Grantee: Francis P. Harrison, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 May 26 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #50
  - File No.: 568, Grantee: William L. Brinkley, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 July 10 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #40
  - File No.: 569, Grantee: Lilly Robinson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 July 22 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #42
  - File No.: 570, Grantee: Martin Pierson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 July 23 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #54
  - File No.: 570, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Martin Pierson, Type: Esmnt, 1953 October 14 (Box 10)
    County:, Comments/Location: Easement
  - File No.: 571, Grantee: Samuel Agnello, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 July 24 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #11
  - File No.: 572, Grantee: Kenneth R. Pfeiffer, Grantor: Duke, 1953 July 24 (Box 10)
    Map-Block-Lot: Lot #10
  - File No.: 573, Grantee: William A. Kale, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 July 31 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #13
  - File No.: 574, Grantee: William J. A. DeMario, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 July 31 (Box 10)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #8
  - File No.: 575, Grantee: H. Shelton Smith, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 4 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 576, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John M. Fein, Type: Esmnt, 1953 October 16 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Comments/Location: Easement
  - File No.: 577, Grantee: Robert L. Dickens, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 January 22 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #44
  - File No.: 578, Grantee: Thomas A. Schaefer, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 16 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #3, Comments/Location: Section I
  - File No.: 579, Grantee: James L. Price, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 7 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #43
  - File No.: 580, Grantee: Clarence Gohdes, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 21 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #41
  - File No.: 581, Grantee: Alexander DeConde, Grantor: Robert L. Dickens, Type: Deed, 1954 January 22 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 582, Grantee: Henry Weitz, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 25 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #48
  - File No.: 583, Grantee: Kenneth Penrod, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 25 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #32
  - File No.: 584, Grantee: Joel Colton, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 25 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #34
  - File No.: 585, Grantee: Richard L. Tuthill, Grantor: Edmund Perry, Type: Deed, 1954 August 26 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #23
  - File No.: 586, Grantee: John B. Hickam, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 26 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #49
  - File No.: 587, Grantee: Alfred N. Costner, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 August 25 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #53
  - File No.: 588, Grantee: Edward Kraybill, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 September 10 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #51
  - File No.: 589, Grantee: Carl H. Stoltenberg, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 September 11 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #29
  - File No.: 590, Grantee: Theodore B. Schwartz, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 September 11 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #28
  - File No.: 591, Grantee: Leon Chaiken, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 September 14 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #30
  - File No.: 592, Grantee: Loren R. Withers, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 September 23 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: 178-01-031, Comments/Location: Lot 31, Sec. 2, Duke Homesites, 2733 Dogwood Dr
  - File No.: 593, Grantee: Joseph B. Parker, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 September 23 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #24
  - File No.: 594, Grantee: Trogler F. Adkins, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 October 14 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #56
  - File No.: 595, Grantee: Arlin Turner, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 October 20 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #20
  - File No.: 596, Grantee: Harry Ashton Owen, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 October 29 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #17
  - File No.: 597, Grantee: Paul Welsh, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 October 29 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 598, Grantee: Wayland E. Hull, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 October 29 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 15-16 & 46
  - File No.: 599, Grantee: Frank L. Engel, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 October 29 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #6, Comments/Location: Section I, Duke Homesites
  - File No.: 600, Grantee: Fred W. Whitener, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 November 9 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #22
  - File No.: 601, Grantee: Allan M. Cartter, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 November 9 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #21
  - File No.: 602, Grantee: H. A. Strobel, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 November 9 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #19
  - File No.: 603, Grantee: William G. Anlyan, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 November 12 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 604, Grantee: Wallace H. Jensen, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 November 18 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 605, Grantee: Ewald W. Busse, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 December 11 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 606, Grantee: Lewis J. McNurlen, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1953 December 31 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #45
  - File No.: 607, Grantee: Otto H. Gauer, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 January 6 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 608, Grantee: McMurry S. Richey, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 January 6 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #27
  - File No.: 609, Grantee: Creighton B. Lacy, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 January 6 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 610, Grantee: Lionel W. McKenzie, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 January 6 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 611, Grantee: William H. Gardner, Jr., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 January 22 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 612, Grantee: John A. Fowler, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 January 29 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 613, Grantee: Marten J. Luvaas, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 February 22 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #39
  - File No.: 614, Grantee: James H. Phillips, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 March 16 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #7-A
  - File No.: 616, Grantee: Juan R. Castellano, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 February 14 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H-9,A/R
  - File No.: 617, Grantee: Howard Haines, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 April 15 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #38
  - File No.: 618, Grantee: Juan R. Castellano, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 March 31 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H8R
  - File No.: 619, Grantee: Russell A. Frazier, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 May 27 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 1-6,Blk.2
  - File No.: 620, Grantee: Jack G. Robbins, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 May 28 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lots 15-16,46
  - File No.: 621, Grantee: John H. Hollowell, Grantor: Alfred N. Costner, Type: Deed, 1954 May 28 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 623, Grantee: James V. Warren, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1954 June 11 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #14
  - File No.: 624, Grantee: State of N.C., Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed/Copy, 1954 July 15 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 626, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Otto Gauer, Type: Deed, 1954 November 5 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 221, Page: 574, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #2, Comments/Location: Duke Homesite, Sec. 1
  - File No.: 628, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Charles Duval, Type: Deed, 1954 December 10 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 629, Grantee: Frank L. Engel, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1957 July 13 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 630, Grantee: Thomas Winner, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 January 7 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #6
  - File No.: 631, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: William A. Kale, Type: Deed, 1955 January 20 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 632, Grantee: Henry F. Bowers, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 February 14 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #H9B/R,H10R
  - File No.: 633, Grantee: Karl M. Wilbur, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 February 28 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot H/-42
  - File No.: 634, Grantee: Albert Heyman, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 March 15 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 635, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Wallace Jensen, Type: Deed, 1955 April 5 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 636, Grantee: Bernard Bressler, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 May 9 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 637, Grantee: Andrew D. Foster, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 May 24 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 638, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: John B. Hickam, Type: Deed, 1955 June 6 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 639, Grantee: Robert M. Colver, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 June 16 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 640, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Morten J. Luvaas, Type: Deed, 1955 December 15 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 641, Grantee: John R. Alden, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 December 15 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 642, Grantee: Duke, Grantor: Thomas Winner, Type: Deed, 1955 December 19 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Deed Book: 231, Page: 80, Comments/Location: Woodburn Road, Homesites, Sec. 1
  - File No.: 643, Grantee: Raymond W. Postlethwait, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 May 19 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 644, Grantee: James H. Phillips, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1956 April 24 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 645, Grantee: Walter Gordy, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1956 April 24 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #37
  - File No.: 646, Grantee: E. Charles Kunkle, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1956 May 3 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 647, Grantee: Hornell N. Hart, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1956 April 24 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 648, Grantee: Philip Handler, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1956 May 3 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #35
  - File No.: 649, Grantee: Leonard Carlitz, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1955 September 12 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot ?
  - File No.: 650, Grantee: Robert H. Woody, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1956 December 14 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 652, Grantee: George J. Baylin, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1957 April 30 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 653, Grantee: Nicholas G. Georgiade, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1957 April 30 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #33-34
  - File No.: 654, Grantee: Gregory A. Kimble, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1957 April 30 (Box 11)
    County: Durham, Map-Block-Lot: Lot #31
  - File No.: 655, Grantee: John M. Dozier, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1957 April 30 (Box 11)
  - File No.: 656, Grantee: Louis E. Swanson, Grantor: Duke, Type: Deed, 1957 April 30 (Box 11)